<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Photos on Tai Vong</title><link>https://vchitai.github.io/photos/</link><description>Recent content in Photos on Tai Vong</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://vchitai.github.io/photos/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Busan, South Korea</title><link>https://vchitai.github.io/photos/kr-busan/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://vchitai.github.io/photos/kr-busan/</guid><description>Busan is the second-largest city in South Korea, located on the southeastern coast of the Korean Peninsula. It is the capital of Busan Province and is known for its beautiful beaches, vibrant culture, and historical sites.</description></item><item><title>Daegu, South Korea</title><link>https://vchitai.github.io/photos/kr-daegu/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://vchitai.github.io/photos/kr-daegu/</guid><description>Daegu is a city in South Korea, located in the southeastern part of the country. It is the capital of Daegu Province and is known for its beautiful beaches, vibrant culture, and historical sites.</description></item><item><title>Seoul, South Korea</title><link>https://vchitai.github.io/photos/kr-seoul/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://vchitai.github.io/photos/kr-seoul/</guid><description>Seoul is the capital city of South Korea, located in the southeastern part of the country. It is known for its beautiful beaches, vibrant culture, and historical sites.</description></item><item><title>Beijing, China</title><link>https://vchitai.github.io/photos/cn-beijing/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://vchitai.github.io/photos/cn-beijing/</guid><description>Beijing is the capital of the People&amp;rsquo;s Republic of China, the world&amp;rsquo;s third most populous city proper, and most populous capital city. The city, located in northern China, is governed as a municipality under the direct administration of the central government with 16 urban, suburban, and rural districts. Beijing is mostly surrounded by Hebei Province with the exception of neighboring Tianjin to the southeast; together, the three divisions form the Jingjinji megalopolis and the national capital region of China.</description></item><item><title>HangZhou, China</title><link>https://vchitai.github.io/photos/cn-hangzhou/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://vchitai.github.io/photos/cn-hangzhou/</guid><description>Hangzhou is the capital and most populous city of Zhejiang, People&amp;rsquo;s Republic of China. It sits at the head of Hangzhou Bay, which separates Shanghai and Ningbo. Hangzhou grew to prominence as the southern terminus of the Grand Canal and has been one of the most renowned and prosperous cities in China for much of the last millennium. The city&amp;rsquo;s West Lake, a UNESCO World Heritage site, immediately west of the city, is among its best-known attractions.</description></item><item><title>Wuzhen, China</title><link>https://vchitai.github.io/photos/cn-wuzhen/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://vchitai.github.io/photos/cn-wuzhen/</guid><description>Wuzhen is a historic scenic town, part of Tongxiang, located in northern Zhejiang Province, China. It lies within the triangle formed by Hangzhou, Suzhou and Shanghai. Wuzhen&amp;rsquo;s area is 71.19 km². The town has a total population of 60,000, of which 12,000 are permanent residents.</description></item><item><title>Shanghai, China</title><link>https://vchitai.github.io/photos/cn-shanghai/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://vchitai.github.io/photos/cn-shanghai/</guid><description>Shanghai is one of the four direct-controlled municipalities of China and the most populous city proper in the world, with a population of more than 24 million as of 2017. It is a global financial center and transport hub, with the world&amp;rsquo;s busiest container port. Located in the Yangtze River Delta, it sits on the south edge of the estuary of the Yangtze in the middle portion of the East China coast.</description></item></channel></rss>